cellunlocker.net 2016-06-28

# Privacy Statement | Cellunlocker.Net

## Privacy Statement

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. If you have any questions/comments about privacy, please do not hestiate to contact us.

The following statements define Cellunlocker‘s privacy policy. The terms of this policy apply to www.cellunlocker.net  unless different terms are specified in an online form, or other form or contract provided to you. By submitting your information to Cellunlocker, you are consenting to the following Terms & Conditions, and to respect the proprietary notices.

**Information We Collect**

Cellunlocker collects information from users of our Website, potential clients, prospective employees, and alliance relationships to name a few, including the information you provide to us by submitting information to us through use of the site.

Cellunlocker does not collect your personal credit card information, this information is processed and remains with our trusted processing partners.

In certain circumstances (e.g., when you subscribe to a mailing list or send us a request for quotation), we may ask you to provide your name, e-mail address and certain other information.

**How will we be using the information you provide?**

The information collected by Cellunlocker will allow us to personalize our working relationship with you and, with your consent, to occasionally send you information about our services.

Cellunlocker does not sell or rent any confidential information about our customers to third parties.

Cellunlocker may provide your personal information to companies who are engaged by Cellunlocker to process your unlock order (e.g. unlock code, software, solution).  
These companies will not use the information for other purposes.

Furthermore, unless you opt out, we also use the information to send you updates regarding special offers and promotions, new services and noteworthy news and events. You may, at any time request that we stop using your personal information by simply e-mailing us.

**Information Sharing And Disclosure**

Cellunlocker does not provide information about you, except as set forth herein:

We store your information in our database and do not plan to share it with third parties. If we ever need to share this information with other third parties, we will notify you. At any time you can remove your name and related information from our database, and we will provide you a choice to opt-out if you don’t want your information used for any purpose. You can review and update your information by contacting us.

We will release specific information about you only if we are compelled to do so to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, court, administrative or governmental order or other legal process, or in the unlikely situation where we, in good faith, believe such information is necessary to prevent harm to you or others.

If we believe it is necessary to share your information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of Cellunlocker’s terms of use or as otherwise required by law we will provide the information collected.

In the event of a corporate reorganization, either by an operation of law, merger or purchase of assets, your information may be subject to a different privacy policy which we will make available on our website.

**Links to Other Websites**

The Cellunlocker Web site includes links to Websites operated by other organizations Cellunlocker has absolutely no control over the operation of these Web sites, and their presence on our Website does not represent an endorsement. Any personal information that you may provide to the operators of these Web sites is subject to the specific privacy policies that apply to the individual sites.

**Privacy Complaints**

If you believe that Cellunlocker has not complied with the provisions of this privacy policy, please email us your concerns, [sales@cellunlocker.net](mailto:sales@cellunlocker.net).  

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

Cellunlocker reserves the right to change or enhance the provisions of this privacy policy to improve our service to you from time to time. This is not a contract. If we do change our policy, the change will be highlighted within our posted privacy policy. The new provisions will be effective as soon as they are posted. Please check this page whenever you visit our site to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

The following statements define Cellunlocker‘s privacy policy. The terms of this policy apply to www.cellunlocker.net unless different terms are specified in an online form, or other form or contract provided to you. By submitting your information to Cellunlocker, you are consenting to the following, and to respect the proprietary notices.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us with your questions at:

**Cellunlocker  
**5177 164th Ave Bellevue, WA 98006  
1-800-507-9077 or sales@cellunlocker.net
